https://keeper.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy - The Keeper Inc./Moon Cup Co.
Login / Register0 items - $0.00Subscribe via RSSE-mailFollow us on TwitterConnect with us on FacebookPinterestLinked In The Cup that Created the Menstrual Cup Industry A Women and Family Owned Business Manufacturing Menstrual Cups since 1987
The Creator of the Menstrual Cup IndustryLearnQ and AMyths and ObjectionsWho is it for?How do I use it?UsageCleaningThird World CountriesWhy is it important?Resources & LinksMenstrual Product ArticlesAudio InterviewsOur favsAboutOur ValuesOur StoryPressBecome a Brand Affiliate!ResourcesThe CostLogos and PhotographsTestimonialsOrderShop OnlineOrder by PhoneOrder By MailReturn PolicyRetail StoresBlogContact Us Privacy Policy Home
Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy (Updated May 24, 2018)The Keeper Inc. and Keeper.com has a very strict privacy policy, applying to all information collected by this website. On this page, you will find:What personally identifiable information can be collected through this siteHow that personal data is usedWho that personal data may be shared withUsers’ options regarding how their personal data is usedSecurity measures put into place to protect personal dataHow users can correct any inaccurate personal dataHow users can have their personal data permanently deleted from our databaseAll personal data is protected by a variety of international privacy laws including in the United States, Canada, the European Union, and any other jurisdictions with privacy laws in place. Our services are fully compliant with the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR), used by the European Union to protect their citizens’ data.Collection of Personal Information The Keeper Inc. only collects personal data that has been voluntarily provided by the users of this site by signing up for our ezine or other promotional emails. We are the sole owners of the data collected on this site.Detailed personal information may be collected when an order is placed, with that information being used to verify the identity of the client and to process their order in terms with our merchant bank. This information may also be used to provide professional services, as contracted by the client.We do not knowingly collect the personal data of any individuals under the age of 18 years old in any jurisdiction. If such information is collected and discovered, it will be completely deleted from our records and database.Use of Personal Information The Keeper Inc. may use personal data and information to:Send marketing emails, including ezines, promotions, or notices of new products and services. These services may be opted out at any time by hitting the unsubscribe button within the email or contacting us directly.Directly respond to inquiries through our website, regarding any reasons that we were contacted.Any personal data or information, including email address, will never be sold, rented, lent, or given to any third-party for any reason, with the exception of being legally compelled to when required by the law.Your Access and Control Over Your Information At any time, users may opt out of any future contact with this website. By contacting us, users may also:See their personal data that we currently holdCorrect or change any of their personal dataRequest deletion of their personal data, also known as ‘being forgotten’, which we will execute immediatelyAsk any questions about how we use their personal dataExpress any concerns they may have about our use of personal dataData Security Your personal data security is very important to us.The Keeper Inc. has built our website using industry-standard security measures and authentication tools to protect the security of all personal data collected. We, and the third parties who provide services for us, also maintain technical and physical safeguards to protect personal data.When credit card information is collected through our website, it will be encrypted using industry-standard technology for conducting secure online transactions.Use of Third-Party Tools The Keeper Inc. uses a variety of third-party online services and tools on our website.Mailchimp is used for email marketing purposes, including our weekly newsletters, promotions, and news about our services.The use of these third-party tools is covered by the privacy policies of these third-parties. Please refer to the privacy policies for any questions regarding the use of these tools.E-Commerce Orders To provide e-commerce services, we require personal contact information, including full name and billing information, along with financial information, such as credit card numbers and expiration dates. This data will be used for billing purposes only. If there is a problem with the order, this personal information will be used to contact the user.Cookies “Cookies”, small pieces of tracking data used on most websites, are used on our site and may be used to track repeat visitors’ engagement with our site and improve access. These cookies will be stored on the users’ hard drive. Cookie use is not connected to any personally identifiable information collected on our site through other means, such as email signups.Personal Contact We will not contact you unless you have specifically requested information from us.We dislike spam, junk mail, popup ads and the like just as much as you do. All newsletters that are sent by Keeper.com include an unsubscribe link in them. Users can remove themselves at any time from our newsletters by clicking on the unsubscribe link.Links to Other Websites This website contains links to other websites, including client websites, social media services, affiliate links, and sites related to the services that we offer. The Keeper Inc. is not responsible for the privacy policies or CDPR compliance of any third-party website.Updates to this Statement This privacy policy may be updated from time to time as necessary to comply with international privacy laws. You will always be able to find this updated policy on our website. Please check this page occasionally to ensure that you are aware of any changes made.Contact Us If you have any questions about this privacy policy, how The Keeper Inc. treats your personal data, or you wish to change your personal information, you can contact us at:Phone: 800-500-0077 Email: info@keeper.comShare...FacebookTwitterLinkedinTumblrDiggFlattrPinterestBufferRedditStumbleUponemailVKYummlySusbscribe for Sustainable Tips & Specials Email Address
Tags2015 bulk coconut oil compost diy Earth Friendly Easy eco holidays eco home environment family farmers market food giveaway green holidays green home green living handmade health health and wellness herbs holiday Holidays home homemade kids Made in the USA meat Recycle recycling reduce reusable Reuse summer sustainability tampons The Keeper Inc. trash travel Upcycle waste wellness women womens health Zero WasteShare ButtonsFacebookTwitterLinkedinTumblrDiggFlattrPinterestBufferRedditStumbleUponemailVKYummlyPrivacy PolicyOur StoryOur ValuesCleaning Your CupsWho Uses The Keeper and Moon Cup Menstrual Cups?Menstrual Cup Myths and Common ObjectionsOur Products
The Moon Cup (Click here for more details)
$35.00
The Moon Cup - Ocean Blue
$35.00Recent PostsMenstrual products now qualify as a medical expense23 Apr 2020Eco Gift Ideas for Everyone On Your List05 Dec 2019find us on facebookOur StoryOur ValuesCleaning Your CupsWho Uses The Keeper and Moon Cup Menstrual Cups?Menstrual Cup Myths and Common ObjectionsCopyright © 2014 The Keeper, Inc.Subscribe via RSSE-mailFollow us on TwitterConnect with us on FacebookPinterestLinked In
